The perfect man. The perfect story. The perfect murder.
Scoop is a comedy, mystery film directed by Woody Allen.
An American journalism student in London scoops a big story, and begins
an affair with an aristocrat as the incident unfurls.
Sondra Pransky, played by Scarlett Johansson.
Sid Waterman, played by Woody Allen.
Peter Lyman, played by Hugh Jackman.
Joe Strombel, played by Ian McShane.
Mr. Malcolm, played by Charles Dance.
Vivian, played by Romola Garai.
Scoop is a 2006 romantic crime comedy film written and directed by Woody Allen and
starring Hugh Jackman, Scarlett Johansson, Ian McShane and Allen himself.
It was released in the United States by Focus Features on July 28, 2006.
The film follows an American journalist and a magician being guided by the spirit of a
reporter to investigate a British aristocrat who might be a serial killer.
Scoop received mixed reviews from critics regarding its humor, but was a
box-office success, grossing $39 million against a $4 million budget.
The film explores themes of daughter, newspaper,
journalist, prostitute, drowning.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.